===============OP=================
===============ED=================
Black Knights... BANZAI!!!
黒の騎士団…　万歳～！
万歳～！
What happened to the Knightmare that saved Zero?
ゼロを助けた　ナイトメアは？
It got out using the route Xing-ke gave it.
星刻のルートで　外に出した
Xing-ke?
星刻？
The Chinese Federation guy I told you about.
さっき話した　中華連邦の人
I see. Then I'll make use
of that route as well.
そうか　なら私も使わせてもらうとしょう
So, was that pilot the same
one from Babel Tower?
で　そのパイロットはバベルタワーの？
Because of what happened to Urabe,
I won't tell you his name.
卜部の件が　あるからな…
名前などは伏せるが
Just think of him as
someone who supports us.
我々の賛同者と考えていい
Did you use your Geass on him?
相手に　ギアスを使ったのか？
It turned out I didn't need to.
当面は　必要なくなった
Anyway C.C.,
about the Emperor and...
それより　C.C.　皇帝に…
Hold it! Are you keeping that
pilot a secret from me, too?!
ちょっと待って！
私にも　パイロットのことは　秘密なの？
So what? There are times
I like to keep secrets, too.
いいだろう？
秘め事ぐらい持ちたいときもある
Is that you speaking
as Zero or as Lelouch?
それは　ゼロとしめ？ルルーシュとして？
It's not like everyone knows
about our relationship, right?
君との関係も　オープンにはしていないだろう？
Hey! Quit saying weird stuff like that!
ちょっと　変な言い方やめてよ！
What about Zero's true identity?
ゼロの正体は？
Kallen and I are the only ones in the
organization who know the truth.
知っているのは組織内で私たちだけとなったが…
Keep that secret, too.
それも　伏せよう
Lelouch, may I go on being captain of
Zero's personal guard, as I have been?
ルルーシュ
私は　今までどおり　ゼロの親衛隊隊長でいいのかしら？
Yes.
ああ
Understood. Aye, aye, sir!
分かりました　了解です
I'm counting on you.
よろしく頼む
We'll talk about the Geass later.
We have more pressing matters.
ギアスのことは　あとで話そう
それより　今は…
Right. Understood.
ああ　分かっている
Oh, man!
I've missed my old uniform!
おお　懐かしの団員服！
Rock and ROLL!
よっしゃ～！
I can't believe they
had all this ready for us!
よくこんなの用意してたよな
They say Capt. Kouzuki
and Mr. Urabe prepared it for us.
紅月隊長と卜部さんが準備していて
Man...
I see.
So, Urabe died well, you say?
そうか…卜部は　立派に逝ったか
Yes, sir.
はい…
You should just confess, already!
告白しちゃえばいいのに
Wh- What do you mean, "confess?"
なっ…何を告白しろと…
It's Zero!
ゼロだ！
Zero?
ゼロ？
Zero!
Hold it! Hold it!
待て待て！
We appreciate your rescuing us,
助けてもらったことには感謝する
but we wouldn't have been captured in
the first place if you hadn't betrayed us!
だが　お前の裏切りがなければ　私たちは捕まっていない
Don't you owe us an explanation?
ひと言あっても　いいんじゃない？
Zero, what happened?
ゼロ　何があったんだ？
Everything is for victory over Britannia.
すべては　ブリタニアに勝つためだ
Right. And?
ああ　それで？
That's all.
それだけだ
You have nothing else to say?!
No excuses? No apologies?
ほかにないの？
言い訳とか　謝罪とか
Stop it!
やめろ！
ゼロ…勝つための手を打とうとしたんだな？
Zero, were you trying to give
us a better chance of winning?
I always have my eye
on getting results.
私は常に結果を目指す
I understand.
分かった
There are times when operational
details must be kept secret!
作戦内容は伏せねばならないときもある
Right now, we need his power!
今は　彼の力が必要だ
I can't think of anyone more
capable than he is!
私は　彼以上の才覚をほかに知らない！
I agree!
Everyone, let's trust Zero!
オレもそうだ　みんな　ゼロを信じよう！
But Zero treated you like a pawn.
でも　ゼロは　お前を駒扱いして…
Who else but he could
have pulled this off?!
彼以外の誰に　こんなことができる？
Even the Chinese Federation isn't
strong enough to wage war on Britannia!
ブリタニアと戦争するなんて　中華連邦だった無理だ！
And the E.U. continues to lose
to Prince Schneizel, right?
EUも　シュナイゼル皇子の前に負け続けているらしいじゃないか
We're the hope of all of the colony Areas!
オレたちは　すべての植民エリアにとって希望なんだ！
Zero is the only one who can lead us
to victory in our war of independence!
独立戦争に勝つためにも
オレたちのリーダーは　ゼロしかいない！
He's right!
Zero! Zero! Zero! Zero!
そうだ！
ゼロ…
Zero! Zero! Zero!
Asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
星になるよ 君守る
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
戦いは行方知らず
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
明日と昨日の交差点で
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
交わらない君と僕
ima iku yo boku wa nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, on my way right now
今行くよ 僕は流れ星
sekai ga kuchihatetemo
Even if the world crumbles apart
世界が朽ち果てても 変わることの無いものがある
kawaru koto no nai mono ga aru
There are things which will never change
namida wo koraete demo
Even as we bear tears in our eyes
涙を堪えてでも 守るべきものが僕らにはある
mamorubeki mono ga bokura ni wa aru
There are things we must protect
nanman'nen nan'okunen mae kara no
A message that's been in my body
（nononono）
遅れまいと メッセージが絶えない
message ga tainai de
For thousands and millions of years,
（no）
uzukidasu... mayoi wa nai
Springs out... I have no reservations
剥き出す 撃ち抜く
（迷いは無い）
narihibiku... kantan da
Roars out... It's easy
（簡単だ）
shagareta koe de... asu wo yobu
In a hoarse voice... Calling tomorrow
しゃがれた声で 傷だらけの手で 君守る
kizudarake no te de... kimi mamoru
With my wounded hands... I protect you
I continue to fight...
way got you could like
I continue to fight!
asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
星になるよ 君守る
戦いは行方知らず
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
明日と昨日の交差点で
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
交わらない君と僕
sadame wo kirisaku nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, tearing fate apart
宿命を切り裂く流れ星
afureru kimi no namida boku ga ima ubaisaru
I'll take away your overflowing tears right now
溢れる君の涙 僕が今奪い去る
KNIGHTS OF THE ROUND
本日付けをもちまして
From this day forward, I am returning
to class here at Ashford Academy.
このアッシュフォード学園に復学することになりました枢木スザクです
I'm Suzaku Kururugi.
I look forward to working with you all.
よろしくお願いします
枢木スザクって…ゼロを捕まえた？
Suzaku Kururugi?!
The guy who caught Zero?
The White Death
is coming to school here?
白き死神が　学校に？
あれが　ナイトオブセブン様
That's the Knight of Seven!
But, he's an Eleven...
でも　イレヴンだし…
Who cares?!
He reports directly to the emperor!
関係ないって　皇帝陛下直属よ
Okay, quiet down!
は～い　静かにする！
Sir Kururugi has been reassigned to Area 11
and he's coming back to school here.
枢木卿はエリア１１配属に伴い　復学することとなった
席は　とりあえず　ルルーシュの隣に
You can take the desk
next to Lelouch for now.
はい
Yes, ma'am.
スザク…　お前は
Suzaku... You...
K
U
R
G
I
オレの初めての友達だった
でも　戦争が僕たちを引き裂いた
You were my first real friend.
But the war tore us apart.
第２次太平洋戦争　ブリタニアによる日本制圧
The Second Pacific War,
by which Britannia took control of Japan.
敗戦国日本は　ブリタニアの植民エリアとなった
After its defeat,
Japan became a colony Area of Britannia.
故郷に捨てられたオレ
I, who was abandoned
by my homeland...
故郷を捨てさせられた僕
I, who abandoned my homeland...
再開したときは　敵と味方
When we were reunited,
we were enemies.
僕は　日本人でありながらブリタニアの軍人
While I'm Japanese,
I am also a Britannian soldier.
オレはゼロ　互いに　正体を隠し…
I am Zero.
We both hid our true identities.
We fought each other.
僕たちは　戦った
だが　それは　真実の記憶
However, those are memories
of what truly happened.
皇帝陛下が　書き換えた記憶は　三つ
The emperor rewrote
three things in his memory.
ナナリーのこと
About Nunnally...
ゼロに関する記憶
Any memories concerning Zero...
And that I was a Britannian prince.
そして　オレがブリタニアの皇子だったということ
つまり　今のオレたちは…
つまり　今の僕たちは…
And so,
the two of us now...
久しぶりだな　スザク
It's been a while, Suzaku.
懐かしいよ　ルルーシュ
Feels like old times, Lelouch.
スザク君　久しぶり！
Suzaku, it's been ages!
You've really come up
in the world, Suzaku!
出世したよなぁ　スザク
スザク君が　戻ったって！？
Suzaku's back?!
会長　一応授業中ですから…
Miss President!
We're in the middle of class!
Oh, what's with you, Lelouch?
何よ　ルルーシュ　こんなときだけ
You screwed up, Suzaku.
失敗だったな　スザク
ルルーシュという名前だけで　そばに来た
You just heard the name Lelouch
and came right to my side.
つまり　オレのことを知っているからこその行動
In other words, you acted
as though you knew me.
さて　あとは　ロロが　下手なことをしなければ…
Now, to make sure Rolo
doesn't do anything stupid...
And so everyone except us went back home.
Even the teachers!
それでね　私たち以外はみんな帰っちゃったの
先生もよ
ブリタニア本土に？
Back to the homeland?
ああ　だからここでスザクをしってるのはオレたちだけ
Yeah, which is why we're the only
ones here who know you. Right, Rolo?
なあ？ロロ
うっ　うん…
R- Right.
I see. I was wondering why
I didn't recognize anyone here.
そうか　どおりで知らない顔が
なあ　ゼロの顔　見たんだろ？
Hey, you saw Zero's face, right?
What was he like?!
どんなヤツだった？
Was it really a girl?
実は　女のこ！
クロヴィス殿下ってうわさは？
How about those rumors
it was actually Prince Clovis?
Was he a prince from
some other country?
どこかの国の皇子様？
あっ　その…
Um, well...
いいだろ？それぐらい
Come on, surely you can
tell us that, at least.
ごめん　言えないんだ　軍の…
Sorry, I can't. It's a military secr...
アーサー！
Arthur!
You brought him with you?!
連れてきたの！？
お前は…ほんとに　猫が好きなんだな
Oh, you...
You really love cats, don't you?
接触されてみて　何か気づかれた点は？
Did anything leap out at you
in your contact with him?
いえ　特に
No, not especially.
では　やはり対象の記憶は　戻っていないと判断して…
So, we can conclude the subject's
memories haven't returned?
Wait, please.
We need to investigate this further.
待ってください　もうしばらく　調査が必要です
僕らの監視が　信用できないと？
Are you saying you
don't trust our surveillance?
Ｃ．Ｃ．の件も　あるだろう？
There's also the matter of C.C., correct?
君は　今までどおり　弟役を頼む
Keep on playing his little brother,
as you have been.
イエス　マイ　ロード
Yes, My Lord.
生徒会主催で　枢木卿の歓迎会を行うようです
It seems the student council is
throwing you a welcome party.
そこで再度　確認を
Reconfirm your findings then.
分かりました
Understood.
どうしよう…信じていいのかな？ルルーシュを…
What should I do?
Do I dare trust Lelouch?
Sir, could you please overlook all the
irregularities having to do with myself and Rolo?
先生…オレとロロに関するすべてのイレキュラーを見逃してもらえますか？
分かった　そうしよう
Very well. Let's do that.
二人とも　あまり外を出歩くなよ
Don't go off campus
so much, you two.
は～い
Yes, sir.
The only member left now
is Coach Villetta, right?
残るメンバーは　ヴィレッタ先生だけだな？
はい　しかし　枢木スザクがいます
Yeah, but Suzaku Kururugi
is here now. Shall I kill him?
殺しますか？
そういうことは　もうやめろ
Stop doing things like that.
Oh, and another thing...
ああ　それと…
Yes?
はい
変な言葉遣いは　なしにしないか？
Can you stop speaking so formally to me?
We're brothers, right?
オレたち　兄弟だろ？
心配するな　お前のためにも　計画は急ぐ
Don't worry. I'll hurry up with my plan
for your sake, as well.
やってやるさ　日本の独立ぐらい
I'm going to do it.
Japan will gain its independence.
この学校からでも…
Starting with this school.
イワテ…
Iwate.
ワカヤマ…
Wakayama.
トクシマ…
Tokushima.
There are reports from Yamaguchi, too.
ヤマグチからの報告も上がっている
ゼロが現れた途端に　この有様か
Hmpf! Zero shows up again
and now we get this!
ギルフォード卿の不在も影響しているのやもしれん
It may also be an effect
of Lord Guilford's absence.
If this keeps up,
our Sakuradite supply will also be...
このままでは　サクラダイトの供給にも…
エマージェンシー！
Emergency!
Unknown M.R.F. within the perimeter!
未確認MRFが内部に！
What?!
何っ！？
バカな！ここはエリア１１を束ねる政庁だぞ！
Impossible! This is the government
bureau that controls all of Area 11!
なんだ　このあっけなさは！
How was I able to
get in here so easily?
ゆるゆるだな　あきれるほどに
These guys are almost annoyingly sloppy!
エリア１１の防衛線とは　この程度か！
Is this the best Area 11's
defense line has to offer?!
その判断は　まあまあだ
Ah... Your response to me
isn't that bad, though.
Oh?
何者かは知らぬが
I don't know who you are,
but this ends right here!
ここで終わりだ！
失格
Disqualified. That armament shows you
care more about protecting the building.
この武装は　建物を守ることを優先している
しかたない…
Oh, well.
What?!
何っ！？
まさか　この機体は…
Is that machine?!
そういうことですか
So, that's what we're dealing with...
可変ナイトメア·フレーム　トリスタン…
The variable Knightmare Frame: Tristan.
ということは
Which makes you Lord Gino Weinberg,
the Knight of Three, correct?
ナイトオブスリー　ジノ·ヴぁインベルグ卿ですね？
ああ　君たちを試しにきた
Yeah. I came to test you guys.
さあ　私を止めてみせろ
Now, try and stop me!
いいでしょう　私たちも恥をかかされたままでは治まらない
Very well! We can't let this
insult to us go unanswered!
そうそう　本気で頼むよ
Right, right.
Don't hold back on my account.
As you wish!
言われずとも！
Thank you!
ありがとう！
Why, you!
この～！
Stop this!
やめろ
そこまでだ！決着はついた
That's enough! The battle is decided!
それは　ナイトオブセブンとしての判断ですか？
Is that the decision of the Knight of Seven?
そうだ
It is.
おおっ！スザク！
Oh! Suzaku!
ジノ
Gino, I thought I asked you
to bring Lancelot here for me.
ランスロットを持ってきてほしいと頼んだのに
ああ　来週ロイド伯爵と一緒に来るよ
Yeah, but Earl Lloyd is going
to be coming with it next week.
それより　なんだい？この服！
Anyway, what's with that getup?
学校帰りだからね　制服…
It's my uniform.
I've just come here from school.
へえ～　これが…
Oh, so this is it.
ジノ　いくら名門貴族とはいえ　少しは　普通の…
Gino, I know you're from a great noble family,
but can't you act a little more normal?
あの…　重いんだけど…
Also, you're kinda heavy.
Is it over?
おしまい？
Mordred? Anya came along, too?
モルドレッド…
アーニャまで来ていたのか
おしまい？
Is it over?
終わりだってさ　スザクが
Suzaku made me end it!
つまんない
How dull.
これで　戦力は十分すぎるほどそろった
We've now assembled more
than enough firepower here.
ルルーシュ　３日後の歓迎会で
Lelouch, in three days at the welcome party,
everything will be made clear.
すべてを　明らかにしよう
Sorry for the wait!
お待たせしました！ただ今より
ただ今より　ナイトオブセブン歓迎会を始めま～す！
We will now begin the welcome party
for the Knight of Seven!
Guest of honor,
please address the school.
主賓あいさつ！
Um... I don't suppose
I can ask not to say this, huh?
あの…言わないとダメですか？
Of course not!
This is a presidential order!
当然！
会長命令よ！
あきらめろ　学校では　この人がルールだ
Just accept it.
She sets the rules in this school.
あぁ…分かったよ　割り切るから…
All right.
Just give me a minute to prepare.
MEOW!
にゃあ
This way to the horseback riding course!
乗馬体験コースは　こちら～！
兄さん　なんか　趣旨が　ずれてる気が…
Big brother, is this really
appropriate for the occasion?
ミレイ会長だからなぁ
That's because of Milly.
The Prez loves events like this.
イベント好きだし
Besides, she wants to
make up for last year.
それに　去年のリベンジもあるんだろ
Hmm...
What should I do?
I should just...
どうする？やっぱり　兄さんを…
Rolo.
ロロ…
それじゃ　危ないって
I've told you, that's dangerous.
Here, hold your knife like this.
ほら　こうやって…
こう持ってさ
L- Like this?
こ…こう？
Watch out for your hands.
手　気をつけろよ
Right...
うん…
Big Brother.
兄さん…　実は…僕のギアスには弱点が…
The truth is...
my Geass does have an Achilles' heel.
Wow, would you look at that!
Anya, check this out!
面白いなぁ～　アーニャ　ほらこれ
記録
Recorded.
You really love that stuff, don't you?
好きだね　そういうの
なあ　どうする？特にやることはなさそうだし
So, now what? Doesn't look like there's
anything we have to especially do here.
庶民の学校ってのを見学するか？
Shall we take a tour of where
the commoners go to school?
Right, right. I'm in the storehouse
under the school right now.
はいは～い！今　校舎下の倉庫
Where are the spare energy fillers?
エナジーフィラーの予備って　どこに…
Huh? Didn't these belong to Nina?
あれ？ニーナのだったっけ？これ
分かった
Understood.
キュシュウのＦ細胞を通じて
Go through cell F in Kyushu
and make contact with Diethard.
ディートハルトと連絡を取れ
そうだ　ラクシャータを　こちらに…
Right, have Rakshata come here and...
She wouldn't!
まさか！！
Come see us make
the world's biggest pizza!
世界一のピザ　やりま～す！
Can you give me
the details about this?
詳細を教えてくれ
Sure, here you go!
はい　よろしくね
World's biggest pizza!
世界一のピザ！
HEY!
こんな…何しに…
What do you think... you're doing?!
I still have to retrieve something.
あれを回収せねばならない
どうして　あんなものに　こだわる
Why are you so obsessed with that doll?!
Anyway, come with me!
とにかく　こっちへ来い！
My, you come on forcefully, kid!
強引だな　坊や
Shut up, Witch!
黙れ　魔女！
自分の立場を　分かっているのか！？
Don't you understand your situation?!
The emperor is trying to capture me.
皇帝が　私を狙っている　お前を餌にして
And he's using you as bait.
That's right.
Suzaku's here, as well as another.
そうだ　スザクもいるし
それに　もう一人
A woman I can't use my Geass on!
ギアスの効かない女が…
From pretty young girls...
美少女から…アダルティーな　お姉様まで！より取り見取りの
to sexy grownup women!
Welcome to the Swim Club Café,
where you get exactly what you want!
水泳部カフェに　ようこそ！
I'm glad the coach agreed to do this for us!
やっぱり　先生に　やってもらって　よかった～！
Shirley... So help me,
you'll die a 100 times for this!
シャーリー　あとで１００回殺す
If I didn't have to play
teacher for my mission, I'd!
任務でなければ　教師役など…
I used to be a school teacher.
昔　学校の先生　やっていたから
They've confirmed the Guren Mk-II is there.
紅蓮弐式が　確認されています
Kallen must be in the consulate.
カレンは　総領事館にいるんでしょうね
I see. It's hard to judge her. They call
themselves "resistance" fighters, but still...
そう…難しいな
あっちは　レジスタンスって言うけど…
ニーナは　元気ですよ
Nina's doing well.
この前も　学会で論文を…
She just presented a thesis
at the Science Academy.
ガ二メデ完成体にする気かしら？
I wonder if she's planning
to perfect the Ganymede.
Dunno. Unlike Lloyd,
Nina's specialty is... Hm?
さあ？ニーナの専門はロイドさんと違って…
Has Earl Lloyd... mentioned me to you?
ロイド伯爵　何か言ってた？
Nothing.
何も…
It was a shock to him, wasn't it?
あきれてるんじゃない？
留年して　結婚延期だものね
My having to postpone the
wedding to repeat a year at school.
No, the thing about him is...
いや　あの人は！
he's got so many flaws as a person.
人間として　間違っているところが多いから…
Huh?
Arthur! That was Euphy's!
アーサー！
それは　ユフィの…
Suzaku! You're supposed
to wait here for the main event!
スザク君！主役は　ここで待機
What's this?
なんだい？これ…
They're using a Knightmare...
to make a giant pizza?!
ナイトメアで…巨大ピザ？
So? The same person who gave
the emperor his Geass also told Suzaku?
で？皇帝に　ギアスを与え
スザクに教えたのは　同じ人間なのか？
That's right, although you shouldn't
delve into it any further than that.
そうだ
しかし　これ以上知ると…
I'm already involved in this.
もう巻き込まれている
V.V.
V.V.? And did he give
Suzaku a Geass, too?
V.V.?
スザクにも　ギアスを？
いや　それはないようだ
No, it appears not.
Anyway, at your side is...
それより　お前のそばに…
Lulu!
ルル～！
What's up, Shirley?
なんだい？シャーリー
Oh, there you are.
ん？あっ　そっち？
Do you need something?
何か用でも？
あのね　ヴィレッタ先生が　私のこと　避けてるみたいなの
Coach Villetta seems
to be avoiding me.
だから　ルルの方から…
So, I was thinking you should...
Huh? You're alone?
あれ？一人？
Yeah.
ああ
今　誰かと話してなかった？
Weren't you just talking to someone?
Nope.
It's just the two of us here.
いや　ここは　オレと君の　二人っきりだよ
Just the two of us?
二人っきりって…
Oh, no. I've started
feeling that this is my chance.
やばい　チャンスのような気がしてきた
あのれ　ルル
Look, Lulu,
would you consider going ou...
私と…
Sorry, I couldn't quite catch that.
すまない　ちょっと聞き取りづらいんだけど…
Hey! What's the big idea,
whoever you are?!
な　なんですか？あなた！
What are you doing?!
If someone spots you, too!
どういうつもりだ？お前も　人に見られたら…
I came to take Pizza Girl back!
あのピザ女を連れ戻しに来たのよ
Fine, she's in with the tomatoes.
だったら　トマトの中だ
コンテナごと運び出し
Take the whole container and have
Tohdoh or Ohgi command the... WHOA!
藤堂か　扇の指示を…
Who is that?! You're rude!
誰ですか！？失礼でしょ！
くっ…なんて　ぶざまな…
How undignified!
黙ってないで　なんか言いなさいよ！
Quit standing there and say something!
If I say something,
you'll find out who I am!
しゃべったら　私だって　バレちゃうじゃない
Hey! Hold it!
こら　待ちなさい！
Shirley! Leave them alone!
シャーリー！その生き物は…
ルルーシュ！
Lelouch!
Have you seen Arthur?
アーサー　見なかった？
大事に使っていた羽根ペンを…
He's got a valuable quill pen and...
Wait, is he inside this thing?
まさか　この中に！？
No! Cats and tomatoes
don't go together!
いや　猫とトマトはセットではない！
You're supposed to start here, right?
スタート地点は　ここなんだろ？
It can't be... Gino?!
まさか…ジノ？
Yeah!
This commoner school is really fun!
ああ　面白いな　庶民の学校は
Hey! Wait!
おい　待て！
Ooh!
もう
Did I just see Arthur?
今の　アーサー？
Oh, now we'll have
to change the schedule.
もう～　段取り変えなきゃ
Now then, looks like it's coming
out onto the parade route!
さあ　パレッドルートに出たようです
校舎を回ってから　こちらにやってきますよ～！
It'll round the school building first
and then bring them here.
It's a classic Knight,
but it's handling fine.
クラシュックナイトだけど　状態はいいな
Okay, the route's all set, so...
え～っと…ルールもよし
SHAKE TIME!
シェイクタ～イム！
What a blunder!
He's taking Pizza Girl right to the stage!
失態だ　ピザ女が　ステージで！
Let me at least see who you are!
顔ぐらい見せなさいよ！
I am not... cut out... for this stuff!
こんなの　オレのジャンルじゃ…
Charge!
突撃～！
Here he is! The Knight of Seven,
Suzaku Kururugi!
来た～！
ナイトオブセブン　枢木スザクが
アンデス産のアルティメットトマトとともに　登場だ！
He has appeared, along with our
Andes-grown Ultimate Tomatoes!
Okay, come on over!
You're the one we've been waiting for!
さあ　来てくれ
僕らは　君を待っていた～！
Um, except...
んだけど…
There's a different guy inside!
中の人　違いま～す
Whoa! Whoa!
General team!
Look up at the roof top garden!
ジェネラル班！
ルールトップガーデンを見ろ！
なんですか？副会長
What is it, Vice-Prez?
System pattern rouge!
システムパターン　ルージュ
System pattern rouge.
Release fire extinguishing gas. Initiating.
システムパターン　ルージュ
消火用ガス　噴出開始
What's wrong?!
Is it that much of a surprise?!
なんだ　そういう驚かしだったのか！
What the hell's going on here?!
何事だ！？一体！
Sorry. Are you okay?
すまない　大丈夫か？
Oh no, it was my fault.
あっ　いえ　こちらこそ…
Was that?
Recorded. Thank you.
記録　ありがとう
You're welcome.
どういたしまして…
でも　こういうモラトリアムも　ありかな
Well, sometimes you just get these
little filler incidents in life. Fine, then!
まあ　よし
Well? The person who saw you
was from the Swim Club?
それで？カレンを見たヤツは　水泳部か？
It may have been the coach.
先生じゃないかな
Villetta?!
ヴィレッタか？
I didn't get her name,
but the weird thing was...
名前までは…
だけど　変なの
I think I saw her with Ohgi
at the last culture festival.
前の文化祭で　扇さんと一緒にいた人のような…
ヴィレッタが　扇と？
Villetta and Ohgi?
Minami said that Ohgi may have had a
collaborator who reported directly to him.
南さんが言ってた
扇さん直属の地下協力員かも
扇が？オレに秘密を…
Ohgi? He kept a secret from me?!
お前は　こういうことには鈍感だな
You really are very thick when it comes to
these sort of things, aren't you? You see...
それは…
Rolo... You're turned traitor?
ロロが…寝返った？
Villetta Nu. The woman who was awarded the
rank of baron for ascertaining Zero's true identity.
ヴィレッタ·ヌウ
ゼロの正体を　突き止めた功績で男爵位を得た女
But unknown to most,
you are connected to the Black Knights.
だが　裏では　黒の騎士団と通じていた
I never betrayed...
そのような背信を…
Kaname Ohgi.
扇要
If word of your relationship
with him became known,
彼との関係が　知られれば
せっかく手に入れた位も失うことになります
you'd lose that title
you worked so hard to earn.
Why not be reborn as someone new?
新しいあなたに　生まれ変わりませんか？
これ　シャーリーから　預かったのですが
Shirley actually gave me this to give to you,
so the timing here works out nicely.
いいタイミングでした
Happy Birthday, Coach Villetta.
ヴィレッタ先生　ハッピーバースデー
It seems I owe you another debt.
また　君に　借りが出来たようだな
外交特権を使っただけだよ
I just used my diplomatic immunity.
Besides, I'd like to repay
my debt to you as quickly as I can.
それに　こちらこそ　早く借りを　返しておきたいしね
では　もう一つ　頼んでもいいかな？
Then may I ask another favor of you?
なれ合うつもりはないが
I don't like to be colluding with you.
I'd like to get in contact
with the High Eunuchs.
大宦官に連絡を取ってほしい
The only threat remaining
to subdue is Suzaku.
あと　残す攻略は　スザクだけ
Lelouch?
ルルーシュ
The guest of honor should
get to the main stage.
主役はメインステージに　いてくれよ
Hm? Oh, no.
うん？いや…
みんな楽しんでいるみたいだから
Everyone looks like
they're having a good time.
Besides, there's something
I'd like to discuss with you.
それに　話したいことがあってさ
なんだい？
What is it?
I'm planning to become
the Knight of One.
僕はね　ナイトオブワンになるつもりだ
Whoa! That's the greatest
knight in the empire...
おいおい　それは　帝国最高の騎士…
The Knight of One has the privilege of
being given one Area of his choice.
ナイトオブワンの特権に好きなエリアを１つもらえるというのがある
僕は　このエリアを…日本を　もらうつもりだ
I intend to have this Area.
To take Japan for myself.
I've lost precious friends and a woman
which no one can ever replace.
僕は　大切な友達と掛けがえのない女性を失った
I'm going to become so powerful
that I'll never lose anyone else.
これ以上　誰も失わないためにも
力を手に入れる
だから　もう日本人に　ゼロは必要ないんだ
That's why the Japanese
don't need Zero anymore.
Hmm... Indirect rule, you say?
You're trying to make it a protectorate?
ふ～ん　間接統治か
保護領を目指して？
You can ask this person
for the answer.
答えは　この人に…
The new viceroy who's coming to
take charge of Area 11 next week.
来週　赴任される　アリア１１の新総督だ
You want an ordinary student
to talk to the viceroy?
ただの学生が　総督と？
It's Kururugi.
枢木です
Yes, he's right here in front of me.
Yes.
はい　今　目の前に
はい
I don't know what to say.
Getting to speak with such an important person!
困るんだけどなぁ　そんな偉い方なんかと…
Hello? Big Brother?
もしもし　お兄様？
Big Brother, is that you?! It's me! Nunnally!
I'm coming to be the viceroy!
お兄様なのでしょう？
私です　ナナリーです
総督として　そちらに…
Um, can't you hear me?
Big Brother? It's Nunnally.
あの…　聞こえていますか？
お兄様？
ナナリーです！
Mune no naka itsuka hirotta
Someday let's try to pick up and rebuild
胸の中 いつか拾った
Shiawase no kakera atsumete miyou
The fragments of happiness in our hearts
幸せの欠片 集めてみよう
Wasurekaketeita melody
That nearly forgotten melody
忘れかけていたメロディー
色褪せず僕の真ん中に
Iroasezu boku no man'naka ni
Stay vivid, deep inside of me
ありがとう 心から 僕に今があるのはみんなのおかげさ
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
Boku ni ima ga aru no wa minna no okagesa
Everything I have now, I owe to everyone
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
ありがとう 心から 次は僕がみんなにハッピー贈るよ
Tsugi wa boku ga minna ni happy okuru yo
Next I'll send happiness to everyone
Nanimokamo wasurenai yo
I won't forget anything
何もかも忘れないよ あの日の僕も僕だから
Ano hi no boku mo boku dakara
Because I'm still the same as I was that day
Daisuki da yo'tte itsumo
You need me to keep on saying
「大好きだよ」って　いつも言ってあげなきゃ駄目だね
Itte agenakya dame da ne
How much I love you
Namida ga kobore sou na nagai yoru wa
On those long nights, your tears about to overflow
涙がこぼれそうな長い夜は ふっと振り返って
Futto furikaette
Just turn around
足跡を辿るんだ あの日を忘れないように
Ashiato wo tadorun'da
Follow those footprints
Ano hi wo wasurenai you ni
So that you'll never forget that day
Right now, Nunnally is on
the other end of this phone.
スザクが　ナナリーを罠として…
ナナリーを…　ちっ！
Does Nunnally know that I'm Zero?
とれだけ友達の顔をしていようと
No, I doubt that.
お前の本性はオレを　皇帝に売り払った人非人だ！
That's why Suzaku
would try this trick on me.
お前が　ナナリーのそばに　いることは…
If I talk to Nunnally, he'll know
if I've regained my memories.
He's using Nunnally as a trap!
NUNNALLY!
Suzaku! No matter how you may
wear the face of a friend,
your true face is the fiend
who sold me to the emperor!
Just the thought that
you'll be at Nunnally's side!
SURPRISE ATTACK OVER THE PACIFIC